[
  {
    "front": "蘋果",
    "back": "apple"
  },
  {
    "front": "香蕉",
    "back": "banana"
  },
  {
    "front": "橘子",
    "back": "orange"
  },
  {
    "front": "葡萄",
    "back": "grape"
  },
  {
    "front": "西瓜",
    "back": "watermelon"
  },
  {
    "front": "芭樂",
    "back": "papaya"
  },
  {
    "front": "柳丁",
    "back": "lychee"
  },
  {
    "front": "草莓",
    "back": "strawberry"
  },
  {
    "front": "蓮霧",
    "back": "dragon fruit"
  },
  {
    "front": "檸檬",
    "back": "lemon"
  },
  {
    "front": "櫻桃",
    "back": "cherry"
  },
  {
    "front": "蓮子",
    "back": "lotus seed"
  }
]
